evensi.us 2018-12-29

# Evensi | Privacy

**Subject:** _information pursuant to and by effect of Articles 13, 23 and 26 of Legislative Decree no. 30.6.2003 no. 196 (law relating to the protection of personal information) on the protection of personal information._

Pursuant to Article 13 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003, the Data Controller wished to inform you that:

**Personal information you provide to us:** We receive and store any information you enter using our service or provide us with in any other way. The types of personal information collected may include your name, e-mail address, date of birth, Facebook user names, information on the use of our service and browser information. The personal information you provide is used for purposes such as allowing you to comment and manage events, set up an account and a user profile that can be used to interact with other users through the service, improve the content of the service, customize the content displayed and communicate, also on behalf of third parties, promotions and new features.

**Information collected automatically:** When you use our service, Evensi automatically receives and records information from your browser or mobile device on our server logs, including your location, IP addresses, cookie information and the page you requested. We treat this data as non-personal information, unless we are required to do otherwise under current law. Evensi uses this data in aggregate form only. We may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers collectively use our website so that our partners may also understand how often people use their services and our service.

### What are cookies and other similar technologies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize the browser and tell us how and when the pages on our website are visited and by how many people. Evensi cookies do not collect personal information and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other personal information to determine who you are or what your e-mail address is.

### Facebook events

We only extract public events from Facebook users who use our application and the majority of these events are created by the Facebook community.

To keep an event from appearing on Evensi, simply set it as private on Facebook.

Comments with the icon  have been included by Facebook, and we cannot moderate their content.
